couponcactus.com 2009-06-19

# Privacy - Coupon Cactus

  | 

**Coupon Cactus' Commitment to Privacy  
**The Coupon Cactus website is owned and operated by Coupon Cactus, LLC. Coupon Cactus makes every reasonable effort to protect your privacy and has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy and to share with you our information collection and use practices. We encourage you to read this document carefully before sharing any personally identifiable information. It will convey to you what information we collect & how we collect, use, and safeguard that information as well as assist you in deciding what information you are willing to provide which will help you to use our site and services to their full potential.   

**What this Privacy Policy Covers  
**This privacy policy applies solely to [www.CouponCactus.com](http://www.couponcactus.com/). Coupon Cactus may provide links to other websites in a number of different forms which are operated by third parties and Coupon Cactus is not responsible for the privacy policies, information collection and use practices, security, or content of those websites or parties. If you have any questions about the policies or practices of any third party linked to Coupon Cactus please contact them directly. 

**Information Coupon Cactus Collects & How It Is Used   
**Coupon Cactus collects two types of information. The first type is Personally Identifiable Information that you volunteer in order to utilize our services. The second, Non-Personally Identifiable Information, is an anonymous form of data collection utilizing technology such as "cookies" which is collected in a manner that is not visible to you while browsing the Coupon Cactus website. Information collected by Coupon Cactus is stored in the United States and by using our service anyone outside of the United States is authorizing the export of any actively or passively collected information they provide into the United States . 

> __**Personally Identifiable Information:**_  
>  _To receive online coupons and coupon codes via email from our Coupon Alert System we will require your email address. If a user decides to become a member to earn cash back and/or commissions then contact information must be collected to send payments quarterly. In addition, all other submissions of personally identifiable information, such as contacting us about an issue or advertising on our website, is voluntary and will be used solely for its intended purpose. We may use personally identifiable information to contact you for reasons such as new features on our website, valuable offers we feel you would benefit from, to discuss inquiries, and the like. If, at any time, you do not wish to receive such communication, please follow the directions in the Opt-Out paragraph below. We will never sell or disclose your personally identifiable information to a third party unaffiliated with Coupon Cactus, LLC without your prior consent except in connection with a sale or merger involving the service of Coupon Cactus. We may disclose personally identifiable information as required by law or government agency, to establish or in connection with a legal defense, to comply with legal processes, or to investigate suspected fraud or a violation of our Terms of Use Agreement. 
> 
> __**Non-Personally Identifiable Information:**_  
>  _Coupon Cactus may utilize technology such as, but not limited to, "cookie" technology to track non-personally identifiable information in order to improve the users' experience. A cookie is a piece of information that a website puts on your computer to customize or otherwise enhance your interaction with that website. You authorize, by use of the website, the collection of, but not limited to, IP address, browser type, time of visits, web pages viewed, time expended, usage habits, sites visited just before and after our website, and possibly other non-personally identifiable information. In addition, we do not associate your non-personally identifiable information with your personally identifiable information. We may use or disclose non-personally identifiable information for a variety of reasons including but not limited to improving our services or working with third party business partners. As a user you have a choice of providing or not providing cookie information that is collected. You may turn off cookie usage within your web browser as well as remove any cookie information stored by your browser. Please check the help section of your respective browser to perform these functions. 

**No children under 13  
**The services on Coupon Cactus are not directed at children, we have no intention of collecting personal information from children, and we employ every reasonable effort not to collect, use, or disclose any individually identifiable information from children under the age of 13. You can learn more about protecting your child and The Children's Online Privacy Protection Rule by visiting [www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy](http://www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy). You also may call the FTC's Consumer Response Center toll-free at 1-877-FTC-HELP (382-4357), or write Consumer Response Center, Federal Trade Commission, 600 Pennsylvania Avenue, NW, Washington, DC 20580. 

**Security  
**Coupon Cactus, LLC feels that the security of collected information is of the utmost importance. We have employed reasonable physical, electronic, technological, and managerial business practices in an attempt to safeguard and secure all information we collect. However, because of the technological nature of computers and the internet and the human element of the US Mail, we cannot guarantee 100% security of communicated or stored information and thus you should consider all communication with Coupon Cactus as non-confidential and agree that your use of our website demonstrates your assumption of this risk. 

**Opt-Out  
**If at any time you no longer wish to receive the Coupon Alert System weekly email you can unsubscribe by clicking the link at the bottom of the email or by contacting us directly at [Optout@CouponCactus.com](mailto:Optout@CouponCactus.com). We are not responsible for removing your personally identifiable information from any third party which may have previously been provided to that third party in accordance with this policy. 

**Edit Profile  
**If you wish to alter any of your stored information on Coupon Cactus you can sign into the Member Control Panel and go to the Profile tab or you can contact us at [CustomerService@CouponCactus.com](mailto:CustomerService@CouponCactus.com). 

**Terms of Use Agreement  
**Visitation and use of this site and its features is subject to its Terms of Use Agreement which constitutes a legal agreement between the visitor/user and Coupon Cactus, LLC.

**Contact Us  
**If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, personally or non-personally identifiable information, or the practices of this website you can email us at [Privacy@CouponCactus.com](mailto:privacy@CouponCactus.com). You can also write to us at: 

Coupon Cactus   
56 Carletondale Rd.   
Ringwood , NJ 07456 

**Effective Date & Revisions   
**This Privacy Policy is effective as of **January 3, 2007**. Coupon Cactus, LLC reserves the right to update or revise this policy at our discretion without notice.

|
